const info = [

{
    question: "Who is the Candle Pokemon?",
    answer: "Litwick",
    level: "easy",
    image:"litwick"
},
{
    question: "Who is the Chick Pokemon?",
    answer: "Torchic",
    level: "easy",
    image: "torchic"
},
{
    question: "Who is the Sleeping Pokemon?",
    answer: "Snorlax",
    level: "easy",
    image: "snorl"
},
{
    question: "Who is the 'Snow Hat' Pokemon?",
    answer: "Snorunt",
    level: "medium",
    image: "snowrunt"
},
{
    question: "Who is the Disaster Pokemon?",
    answer: "Absol",
    level: "medium",
    image: "absol"
},
{
    question: "Who is the Slacker Pokemon?",
    answer: "Slakoth",
    level: "medium",
    image: ""
},
{
    question: "Who is the Life Pokemon?",
    answer: "Xerneas",
    level: "hard",
    image: ""
},
{
    question: "Who is the 'New Species' Pokemon?",
    answer: "Mew",
    level: "hard",
    image: ""
},
{
    question: "Who is the Temporal Pokemon?",
    answer: "Dialga",
    level: "hard",
    image: ""
},
{
    question: "Who is the Astral Body Pokemon?",
    answer: "Gothitelle",
    level: "hard",
    image: ""
}
]

export default info;